{
  "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "这本书包含了一章美国历史。",
        "answer": "The book includes a chapter on the history of the United States.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "价格包含税费和运费。",
        "answer": "The price includes tax and shipping.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "女性进入劳动力市场促成了许多积极的变化。",
        "answer": "The inclusion of women in the workforce has led to many positive changes.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "我正在为朋友的生日组织聚会。",
        "answer": "I am organizing a party for my friend's birthday.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "她是会议组织者。",
        "answer": "She is the organizer of the conference.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "这家公司非常有条理。",
        "answer": "The company is very well-organized.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "祝你过得愉快。",
        "answer": "I hope you have a nice day.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "我希望我们能找到解决问题的方法。",
        "answer": "I am hopeful that we will find a solution to the problem.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "情况很绝望。",
        "answer": "The situation is hopeless.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "我可以想象在火星上生活会是什么样子。",
        "answer": "I can imagine what it would be like to live on Mars.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "她有丰富的想象力。",
        "answer": "She has a wild imagination.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 13,
        "type": "句子",
        "question": "孩子们写了富有想象力的故事。",
        "answer": "The children wrote imaginative stories.",
        "textbook": "中考",
        "keyPoint": "句型积累",
        "ability": "中英思维"
      }
  ]
} 